[{"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里。", "questionItem": ["4-1=", "2+1=", "2+1+1=", "7-1-3=", "8-2-2=", "7-2-1="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": "{{4-1=;2+1=;7-1-3=};{2+1+1=;8-2-2=;7-2-1=}}", "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里。", "questionItem": ["3+3=", "4+4=", "2+2+2=", "2+3+3=", "1+2+5=", "2+4="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": "{{3+3=;2+2+2=;2+4=};{4+4=;2+3+3=;1+2+5=}}", "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里。", "questionItem": ["3+2=", "1+2+2=", "6-4=", "8-6=", "8-1-2=", "2+0="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": "{{3+2=;1+2+2=;8-1-2=};{6-4=;8-6=;2+0=}}", "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里。", "questionItem": ["2+1=", "2+3=", "4-1=", "5+0=", "9-2-4=", "1+2+2="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": "{{2+1=;4-1=;9-2-4=};{2+3=;5+0=;1+2+2=}}", "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里。", "questionItem": ["2+2=", "1+2+5=", "2+1+1=", "2+6=", "3+5=", "8-2-2="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": "{{2+2=;2+1+1=;8-2-2=};{1+2+5=;2+6=;3+5=}}", "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里。", "questionItem": ["6-4=", "6-2-3=", "7-6=", "8-6=", "2+0=", "9-8="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": "{{6-4=;8-6=;2+0=};{6-2-3=;7-6=;9-8=}}", "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里。", "questionItem": ["6-4=", "1+6+1=", "9-1-6=", "8-6=", "1+6=", "1+2+4="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": "{{6-4=;9-1-6=;8-6=};{1+6+1=;1+6=;1+2+4=}}", "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里。", "questionItem": ["1+5=", "9-1-2=", "6-4=", "9-1-6=", "5-1-2=", "3+3="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": "{{1+5=;9-1-2=;3+3=};{6-4=;9-1-6=;5-1-2=}}", "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里。", "questionItem": ["7-6=", "3+2=", "5+0=", "1+0=", "6-2-3=", "1+2+2="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": "{{7-6=;1+0=;6-2-3=};{3+2=;5+0=;1+2+2=}}", "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里。", "questionItem": ["7-6=", "1+2+2=", "9-8=", "8-1-2=", "6-2-3=", "3+2="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": "{{7-6=;9-8=;6-2-3=};{1+2+2=;8-1-2=;3+2=}}", "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}]